ugi.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy Policy - UGI Utilities

UGI Utilities, Inc. (“UGI Utilities”, “us”, “we”, or “our”) adhere to the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy applies to information that we collect: on the UGI Utilities website, [www.ugi.com](https://www.ugi.com/) (the “Website”); in any electronic communications, via any UGI Utilities mobile or desktop based applications downloaded through the Website; on social media sites operated by UGI Utilities (“UGI Utilities Social Media Sites”); and through mail and telephone communications. This Privacy Policy explains our use and collection of your information.

###### Information you provide to UGI:

Personal Information could include, but is not limited to, information that personally identifies you such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, cell phone number, photographs or material submitted to the Website, UGI Utilities Social Media Sites or sweepstakes or surveys administered by or on behalf of UGI Utilities, or other information such as gender, occupation and demographic information or any other information that is identified as personal information under applicable law.

Users typically volunteer Personal Information when completing forms, registering for sweepstakes, completing a survey, subscribing to services, downloading a mobile or desktop application, posting material or reporting an issue. We do not sell, share, or otherwise distribute to third parties Personal Information without your consent in any way not disclosed in this Privacy Policy.

###### Information we automatically collect:

 ** _Cookies_**  
Some of our web pages utilize cookies and other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small text file that a website transfers to an individual’s computer or other device for record-keeping purposes. For example, we may use cookies to collect information about website activity. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser by accessing your browser settings. You may be able to delete existing cookies within this functionality. However, please be aware that some features of the Website may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies, and therefore, we recommend that your browser settings accept cookies for this Website. Cookies may be used with Third Parties to provide you with interest-based advertising or targeted content, as described below.

 ** _Tracking_**  
Tracking technologies (including Javascript, beacons and pixels) may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; demographic information, click stream patterns; and dates and times that our Website is accessed. However, we reserve the right to use IP addresses and other tracking technologies to identify a visitor when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the Website’s policies, to protect the Website, our customers, or others, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

###### Third Parties and Advertising Uses:

 ** _Third Parties_**  
UGI Utilities may provide third parties, such as business partners, service providers, trusted affiliates and advertisers, with aggregate statistics about our customers, traffic patterns, and related site information. This data reflects site usage patterns gathered during thousands of customer visits to our Website each month but does not contain behavioral or identifying information about any individual member, unless that member has given us permission to share that information. We may also provide log files and other databases of user information to third parties for analysis, so we can get a better understanding of traffic through our Website and thus improve our content offerings. UGI Utilities may also use third party companies to provide delivery of e-mail newsletters and other messages over e-mail as well as the administration of UGI Social Media Sites, customer surveys, mobile or desktop applications, advertising campaigns and/or sweepstakes. UGI Utilities may also provide third parties with Personal Information for the purpose of marketing services related to your utility service. You have the option to tell us not to provide your information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes, and to opt out of such disclosure, see www.ugi.com/choice/restrict-your-account-information.

Additionally, certain links on the Website will lead you to third party sites, pages or services that are not operated by UGI Utilities. UGI Utilities is not responsible for the content, links or updates on these sites. UGI Utilities solely provides these links for convenience and the inclusion of a link does not imply endorsement of the Website. We encourage you to review the sites’ own privacy policies before interacting with them.

UGI Utilities uses Google Analytics to monitor activity on the Website and may assist with advertising. To learn how Google Analytics collects and processes data, please visit: “How Google uses data when you use our partners’ sites or apps” located at [www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners).  
 **  
 _Targeted Advertising_**  
On occasion, we use third-party advertising companies to serve UGI Utilities ads on other websites. Some of these companies may use information (not including your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number) about your visits to UGI Utilities and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.

To learn more about this practice, its benefits, or how to opt-out, see <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> or [www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

Mobile devices often provide unique advertising choice mechanisms. For more information, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choices>.

 ** _Required Retail Choice Disclosure for Pennsylvania Customers_**  
As required by the Pennsylvania Public Utility Commission, UGI Utilities must provide certain customer account information to electric generation suppliers and natural gas suppliers that are licensed to provide service in the UGI Utilities service territories. For more information about this disclosure and how to opt-out of providing this information, www.ugi.com/choice/restrict-your-account-information.

 ** _Required Disclosure to Third Parties, Including the Government, and Potential Company Structural Changes_**  
UGI Utilities reserves the right to monitor and disclose, without your consent, any communications or personal information, whenever requested to do so by courts, government agencies or by law enforcement agencies or to protect the interests or safety of UGI Utilities Website visitors, customers, employees or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Additionally, in the event of a division, assets or a part or all of UGI Utilities is purchased, sold or transferred or is the subject of a potential transaction, customer information will likely be shared for evaluation purposes and included with transferred business assets.

###### Security and Privacy Restrictions:

 ** _Security_**  
UGI Utilities uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information you disclose both in your browsing and your purchases and to only release this information to third parties we believe share our commitment to privacy. Where appropriate, UGI Utilities uses firewalls and places limits on who can access user information databases. UGI Utilities may inadvertently use or disclose your information in ways not contemplated by this Policy or in direct contravention of it. If a situation arises, UGI Utilities will do its best to work with you, but the sole remedy is to have UGI Utilities try and fix the problem as soon as it can. We are not responsible for any breach of security or for the actions of third parties. While unlikely, it is possible for internet transmissions containing Personal Information to be intercepted by others. UGI Utilities cannot ensure the privacy and security of transmissions made to and from the Website while in transit.

 ** _Do Not Track_**  
Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users may be able to set in some web browsers. It allows users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. Currently, the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) does not have established universal standards regarding DNT signals, and therefore, the Website does not recognize DNT privacy preferences.  
 **  
 _Information Provided by Children_**  
UGI Utilities Website is intended to provide general information about UGI Utilities and its services. The Website is intended for adults and not children under the age of 18. UGI Utilities will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years of age or allow children under the age of 13 to use certain features of our Website without the consent of a child’s parent or guardian. UGI Utilities will not knowingly disclose personal information collected from children. If UGI Utilities learns that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information without parental consent on or to the Website or UGI Social Media sites, UGI will take all reasonable measures to delete the information from records and refrain from using it for any purpose, except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or others as required or allowed by applicable law.

###### Your Acceptance of These Terms and Changes to our Privacy Policy:

By using the Website or the UGI Utilities Social Media Sites, you are agreeing to the terms set forth in the UGI Utilities Privacy Policy. UGI Utilities reserves the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this policy at any time. If at any time UGI Utilities changes this Privacy Policy, changes will be posted here or, where appropriate, communicated to you at the email address you have provided to us. Users are responsible for monitoring this Privacy Policy for any changes and we suggest that you bookmark this page and check back periodically for any changes. Your continued use of this Website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept those changes.

Please note that you are responsible for any material you submit. You, and not UGI Utilities, have full responsibility for the message, including its reliability, originality, and any copyright infringement. Any and all rights to materials and ideas submitted to us become the exclusive property of UGI Utilities. This includes any photographs, messages or communications submitted on UGI Utilities Social Media Sites or the Website.

###### Contact Information:

To ask questions or comment on this Privacy Policy, please contact us at:  
Attn: Marketing Department  
UGI Utilities, Inc.  
P.O. Box 13009  
Reading, PA 19612-3009
